16 hours ahead in Melbourne. I don't
even know what's going on back on the
street.
>> What up? What up? What up?
[music]
Got ran over two times because the roads
ARE
>> This is the question that everybody
wants to know and the main reason why I
came here. When traders pass their
funded account and they are [music]
funded, are these traders actually being
backed with real funds or are they not?
[laughter]
>> [__] man. Ladies and gentlemen, has it
been Oh, actually, no. I actually have a
really big superstition. I don't like
being in the room as soon as we just we
just got here from the airport. Let's go
over here. I don't like laying in the
bed right after the airport. We're all
dirty. We were with other people.
>> Yeah, we were with other people in
economy. Actually, you were in economy
[snorts] cuz it's your fault, bro. It
took us [__] 3 days to get here, bro.
>> After missing two flights where I'm in
first class, we go on the only flight
that I have to be in economy.
>> Guys, let me explain to you what we're
doing right now in Australia. First of
all, beautiful view right now. It's
Dude, what day is it, bro? Dude, we left
the States Monday. It's Thursday.
[laughter]
>> Well, this is our beautiful view right
now of uh fog. Not much really not much
to see right now. But let me give you
guys a little bit of what has just gone
down. We left Jake Paul's ranch on
Sunday actually
>> and it's Thursday.
>> Seas on his drive to Atlanta where we I
got Seas $20,000 tickets to be in first
class to come to Australia. He decided
to take his time, listen to music, was
in his feelings, stopped gas, stopped
and ate a sandwich,
>> and we missed our flight. To be fair, I
told you this was the world's biggest
airport.
>> Uh-huh. Uh-huh. And you got lost four
times and we missed
>> the world's biggest airport.
>> And and and we missed our flight. I lost
$40,000 in our flights, right? No big
deal. Alex paid for it, right? Who gives
a [__] Cool. No problem. No issue.
Sleep a day in Atlanta, wake up the next
day. We get on our first connecting
flight to go to LA. And then from LA, we
come to Melbourne. We get on the flight
cancelled,
nerfed. We're kind of missing the fact
that we went to Minianapolis.
>> Oh yeah, that's that's we got on like a
wrong flight, made it to a different
state, then from that state to the other
state. When we tried to go to LA the
second day, flight cancelled. There was
no hotels nearby, so we had to sleep in
the airport. Yeah, long story short, we
left Sunday and we just made it to
Melbourne Sunday. I mean, we made it
here Thursday. Dude, I don't even know
how I'm functioning right now. Moral of
the story is we are on a [__]
mission. We are on a mission to find the
best prop firm for traders. And this is
almost like if it's almost like if the
Matrix doesn't want us to do this, bro.
They have Bro, it's taken us 4 days to
get here. Bro,
>> we literally missed our first flight by
2 minutes.
>> Missed our flight first flight by 2
minutes. Our second flight got cancelled
and our third flight we got sent to a
different state. Like, dude, what the
[__] I say, "Oh, Alex, you're rich. Pay
for a jet." I thought about it. It was
like $300,000. Not the smartest
financial decision when you're
rebuilding a Bugatti, you're building a
compound and uh yeah, just just not
smart to do that. But I was this close.
If we would have missed our last flight,
I it was going down. But moral of the
story, we are here in Australia because
I am on a mission to find the the most
trustable, reliable prop firm. And I
feel like the the Matrix doesn't want me
to do that. I have been speaking to I
say dozens, but realistically like eight
different prop firms. And I've been
offered all different types of deals.
I've been offered six figure a months
with crazy commission. I've been offered
equity in different prop firms. I've
been offered the most creative formats
these different businesses have done in
order for me to get involved with them.
I have said no. I don't want to do this
for a personal gain. It all makes sense
now why all these other trading
influencers push five different prop
firms because they're making an extra 23
$400,000 a month, which is great for
them. I don't need an extra $2 $300,000
a month. Thankfully, I do very well in
what I do, but I really want a reliable
prop firm that I don't have to worry
about my traders trading on. I didn't
realize how profitable prop firms were
until the other day where I called out
what was it like 100,000 traders. I'm
like, if you could [__] out trade me,
if you can out trade me, you got my
respect. [music] If you can't outrade
me,
respectfully, not respectfully, don't
[__] talk about me. A lot of people
claim that they couldn't out trade me
because they have a lack of capital. And
I I got to thinking, I'm like, well,
that's very true. I've been so
disconnected from the value of a dollar
because I've just been trading my
personal money for so long. So, I didn't
really understand that a lot of traders
struggle to become profitable because
they have a lack of capital. They have
to either do very aggressive flips or
they're very restricted to the amount of
trades that they could take because of
these prop firms with these hidden rules
and just basically set out for you to
fail. So, I went on on the hunt, talked
to a bunch of different prop firms, and
I really had a top two, right? After
every other prop firm, I didn't care
about the money. What I cared about is
the actual prop firm process that goes
for the traders. I was left with two,
FTMO and ACAP. So, FTMO, great company,
has been around the longest, probably
the most replicable prop firm in the
industry, but they lack a lot of
modernized updates. They lack a lot of
community aspects. They lack a lot of
communication with the user, right?
Because you're just big, they're
corporate, they're just established,
right? When it comes to AAP, AAP has
custom day trader challenges. They have
actual community aspect in their events.
I have a full notepad of things. Like I
can't show you my Give me a second.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. I
can't Can I show you what I got here?
Hold on. AAP actually has five
regulations. They're the only prop firm
that is connected with Trading View. So
you could trade on Trading View for the
prop firm. No hidden rules. They have
the exact same consistency rules as
FTMO. So basically the exact same
challenges. I like this one that they
are partnered with the largest bank in
the world, Chase. So all of your funds
are in a regulated bank. Depending on
the challenge that you get, you have a
free retry and you don't have to buy
another platform account. It's called
like a reset or something. Moral of the
story, they have a couple of more notes
that I wrote down here. And it really
made me be the most interested in
working with them to the point where
they're like, "Hey, why don't you just
come out to our office and you have a
chat with us? You can see our risk team.
You can see our reserves. You can see
our back end, and if you feel
comfortable, then you can work with us."
And I said, "You know what? No other
prop firm has offered me something like
this. They're all super shady. I never
talked to the founders directly. I'm
always talking to a project manager, a
COO, D. I'm never talking to the guys.
So, I am here. I traveled 26 hours,
technically like 72 hours [laughter]
to come meet these guys here in person.
I've never met other executives at this
level in the space. So, it's very cool.
I'm going to get a lot of insights.
We're going to see the back end of a lot
of things. So, that's what we're here to
do and uh bringing you guys through the
journey. And I feel like I'm getting
jetlagged now. Dude, when was the last
time we showered?
[laughter]
>> So, fun fact, there's actually nothing
to do in Melbourne.
>> Oh, super fun fact. I put all my guys on
a mission. And I'm like, "Yo, I want to
do something fun in Australia."
Everyone's like, "Dude, there's nothing
to do in Australia. It's winter."
>> I was talking to the lady next to me.
I'm like, "Yeah, I'm going to Melbourne
for the first time." She's like, "Why?"
[laughter]
>> I'm like, "What do you mean why?" She's
like, "There's nothing to do cuz it's
cold."
>> We'll find some We'll figure something
out.
>> At least we get to see penguins,
>> dude. Remember in Africa when the
penguin came up to me and almost grabbed
it?
>> Well, this time we got to grab the
penguin.
>> No, dude. I'm going to [__] choke
this.
>> So, moral of the story, I am looking for
one of the best prop friends to work
with. I believe I have one of the best
strategies andmies right now. I'm
building my trading floor. So, I'm
hosting an event where traders are
coming to trade at my trading floor and
learn how to trade. But I didn't realize
that they lack capital. So, this is
where we're going to finalize this final
piece of uh the trading floor that we're
missing. It's almost like what's that
guy's name? Thanos. So, it's like you
got the trading floor, you have the
strategy, didn't have or you have the
broker, and then you don't have the prop
firm. So this is the the final ring.
>> One more. What could it be?
>> Oh, why Thanos has five.
>> Yeah.
>> Trading floor, strategy, broker, prop
firm
people, the traders.
>> I got to find some traders.
>> That's coming soon. So Oh, dude. Is are
these real? Oh, dude. This is nice.
Oh, dude. They're real. I mean, oh [__]
that doesn't [__] matter.
Dear Alex, welcome to the Ritz College
in Melbourne. May you
vin it. I mean, this is what you get,
bro. I paid $20,000 for this [__] bro.
Bro, we already spent like 60 grand. We
haven't even been here for an hour.
Hopefully, this prop is not a scam.
Would have wasted a [laughter]
hopefully would have wasted a week of
our [__] life, dude.
>> You couldn't find a closer prop firm,
>> dude. No, bro. Literally, no prop firms
have an office. No prop firms invited me
out to their space. No prop firms give a
[__] about the traders, bro. All they
care about is sign up, 50% discount.
Give me your money. Give me your money.
100% discount, bro. 100% profit split,
bro. It's like, dude, chill. You know,
like what type of business are you
running, dude? This is an ugly ass gra.
>> Kind of funny, right? Cuz that is really
how the outside looks right now.
Cuz that that is kind of scary, bro. I'm
not going to lie. No one makes you just
want to stay at the top, you know.
[music]
>> All right, ladies and gentlemen, we are
less jetlagged. Our sleep is scheduled.
We're extremely late to our meeting. So,
we're on our way to AAP's office right
now. It's Friday. I hope there's still a
lot of people there right now. It's 2:00
in the afternoon. Did you know they had
a 100 employees or something like that?
>> Are you sure they're not overseas?
>> No. No. Like 100 employees just at this
office or No,
>> it has to be a really big office.
>> I don't know. Like I
>> we're going to need a lot of more rope
to interrogate them.
>> Yeah. I have a lot of very interesting
questions in inside of this right here.
Well, this is my notepad of all the
questions that I have to ask the CEO and
the team. I want to talk to the risk
team. I want to talk to the strategy
team and get to know the reality behind
the scenes of how they run the business.
Do they actually back traders? Do they
not? If they're so about helping
traders, why charge for a challenge?
Make that make sense. I think I know
why, but I want to hear from them. So,
we're going to try and not get lost here
as we go to the office and see what
they're about. 21 hours ago, I posted
that I was in Australia. And these stats
right here are out of the normal when it
comes to the type of engagement. There's
700 shares and 269 replies. This is only
20 hours ago, right? 20 hours ago, I
posted this one that I'm in Australia. I
had over 500 people tell me to meet them
in Australia. But it's like in the mix.
A
>> lot of Aussies,
>> dude.
I didn't know how that many Australians,
bro. But it's like a mix. It's between
Sydney and Melbourne. So, I might do a
meet and greet here in Melbourne
potentially just to meet the Aussies. I
don't really know. So, we're on our way
to the office and let's see what they're
about. If they actually have 100
employees, that'd be crazy. You know, I'
I've never really met an executive like
this in person. So, quite excited. But
you have talked to one.
>> Yeah. I mean, yeah, we've gone on dozens
of meetings for sure.
>> Yeah. Like the owner of
[__] that guy.
>> Are we stuck? The Matrix doesn't want us
to meet these guys.
>> Hey,
>> what's up, man?
>> How are you?
>> Nice to meet you. Welcome to Melbourne.
Welcome to Australia.
>> Pleasure.
>> How you enjoying our beautiful winter so
far?
>> Uh, yeah, I know you told me it was
cold, but I didn't think it was this
cold.
>> I know. I tried to warn you. I tried to
warn you.
>> Yeah, our our trip here was quite
extensive for sure. We had a little bit
of a bumpy path.
>> I heard the team are super excited to
have you here.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They're super pumped.
>> Is there any other tra come out here
like Everyone's been talking about it.
You are coming this way. Oh,
>> here we go.
>> Can't believe you have 100 employees.
>> I can't believe how big it is. I can't
believe the office, the facilities, the
size of the team.
>> How many to show you around?
>> How many guys do you have on the team?
>> I think we got about 150 here in the
office.
>> In this office?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> And then we got teams in like Cyprus,
UK, Philippines,
>> Bulgaria. So, this is just
>> All right. Here we are. Level 37, my
friend.
>> All right. So, thank you very much. It's
>> actually my office. This is very nice.
This is our um this is our kitchen
breakout area.
>> This is where we do like monthly town
halls. We got next week we got a monthly
town hall. We do like all the updates,
all the all the sort of the team
anniversaries, news, etc. And then
obviously like breakout room, drinks on
a Friday, view of the city, view of the
water.
>> It's a pretty nice pretty nice place to
be.
>> You know how to play chess?
>> Definitely don't take it for granted.
Not very well. No,
>> I'm a very bad chess player.
>> I'm very good, actually.
>> Yeah, I'm very skilled.
>> He shits on my trading forum. [laughter]
>> No, we're pretty lucky. I'll show you
where the team is.
>> Still here.
>> Hello.
>> Doing a little walk around the
[laughter] office.
>> Hello. Hello.
>> I want to introduce you. This is our
people and culture team.
>> Okay.
>> Most of them anyway.
>> Yes.
>> The ones who aren't on leave. So, you've
come at like winter holidays. So, lots
of people are away at the moment.
>> Okay.
>> And it's Friday afternoon. So,
>> yeah. Our jet lag got us through.
>> Exactly. You can't you can't film this
wall. This is this is like all private
>> motivational quote wall. So if you want
to add in a motivational quote, feel
free to write something.
>> I I I could add a motivational
quotation.
>> You're
not cheating.
>> You're not trying. My handwriting is not
the best, you know, but [laughter]
>> it's okay. I have to interpret that one
later.
>> Which which is your favorite quote out
of this?
>> Well, this is what I wrote. I'm just
here for my dogs. [laughter]
>> Okay.
>> Anything for my dogs?
>> Yeah, this is this is legal in
compliance.
>> All of this is legal in compliance.
>> All of this is legal and compliance.
>> Okay. All of this. Very cool.
>> This is finance.
>> This is this is finance.
>> This is finance in here.
>> Very cool.
>> That's some numbers.
>> We're interrupting everything.
>> That's our CFO. This is finance. This is
accounts payable. All our financial
reporting systems. Finance. Do
>> you guys have in-house devs that are
here?
All here. Andrew.
>> Here he is. And he's locked in. Andrew's
locked in. And we've locked in.
>> I I hear the music. Debs.
>> His music is
>> Hello,
>> how are you? Alo,
>> nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
>> How are you?
>> Very well.
>> How's it going?
>> Alex,
>> pleasure. How are you?
>> Pleasure. Very good. These are our data
gurus. So these guys are like building
all our backend systems so that when
we're like analyzing trades in real
time, all the insights around pass rates
and payout rates and like which which
challenges are popular, which add-ons
are popular, all that all that stuff
we're getting in real time with
dashboards and
>> so you guys are responsible for the day
trader challenge. Is that you guys?
>> Yeah.
>> Y okay. Okay.
>> I have some questions for you guys
later. [laughter]
>> We're also responsible with some of the
automations helping with uh the report
on that and getting all the numbers for
for your revenue and then also all the
payouts. Okay, cool.
>> Yeah.
>> So, these guys these guys make our life
like 10 times 10 times [laughter]
easier. Otherwise, we're just like
scrambling in the dark,
>> I would imagine. Now,
>> and then and these guys kind of bring it
all.
>> So, you guys understand the challenges
more than anybody?
>> Well, we we we want to think so.
>> We want to think so, but like not the
rules in particular, but uh the data
side of it, how the orders work, life
cycle of an order, how account breaches,
but not the rules like how they breach
or
>> the rules is more technical.
>> Okay. the risk team there team
>> uh and the product team these guys are
more just looking at what's actually
happening
>> right so they don't really necessarily
know why it's happening just telling us
what's happening
>> so basically the data will be able to
help the product team and the risk team
their data and say what would happen if
we did if we change this you know what
would happen if we change the profit
split or the draw down from 8% to 9% or
9% to 8% that [music] say your pay
rate's going to go up by 3% or 4% or
something like that
>> okay
>> right so they kind of they kind of give
us all that data.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> So you guys make it you guys give the
data to the product team to let them
know if they could make it
>> correct
>> harder. Correct.
>> Exactly. Yeah.
>> So those guys give the information we
need to make the decisions about
product. Basically that's the
>> simple in in very simple terms. That's
what that these guys are helping us sort
of with the the insights the insights
that we need.
>> Raman Alex
pleasure pleasure. So these guys are
building the website like updates
>> front end of the website.
>> Front end flows.
>> Shouldn't even notice them. [laughter]
>> If you notice these guys, there's a
problem.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Awesome.
>> This is our security team.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Alex, Jono, how's it going? Nice to meet
you guys.
>> Hey, nice to meet you. We're going.
Pleasure.
>> Nice to meet you, man.
>> Pleasure.
>> Nick, head of security.
>> Never been more important
>> obviously with um
>> like cyber attacks and stuff,
>> all that stuff. So, um, yeah. I mean,
what's a normal week look like for you
guys? Just stopping.
>> Just keeping them out.
>> You don't want to go into that room.
That's a bad room.
>> Why?
>> See the frosting glass?
>> Yeah. Oh,
>> that's bad. That's where you fire
people. [laughter]
>> Don't want to get called into that room.
That's bad.
>> Dude, this is sick.
>> You got to get that one.
>> There's only a few of them here at the
moment. This is our marketing team. So,
Shikica does social media,
>> Nathan does,
>> CRM. So, we work super close with the
marketing team. We're like, okay,
>> talking to them every day, working with
them on different different campaigns
and creatives and um what what's coming
up next. Uh and then customer support is
over here. Again, another like super
important team for us. So, you can start
from
>> there at the moment, [laughter] but
there are people actually live here.
>> Um
>> so I I guess it's Friday afternoon.
>> Friday afternoon. Yeah. Some people
working from home, some people I think I
told you it's like school holidays at
the moment.
>> Yeah. So, um, lots of people are away
with like family going somewhere kind of
somewhere warmer, getting away getting
away from the cold. Um, but yeah,
customer support lives here, so like
super close to us, our team.
>> Um, and this is where we're dealing with
tickets that come in overnight.
>> We've got like a chat, an awesome
chatbot that does like a lot of the work
now as well. So, we're always updating
the chatbot, making sure that's current,
staying up to date with, and then just
dealing with stuff as it comes in,
making sure we're dealing with customer
issues as quickly as they as quickly as
they as they happen. So,
>> uh, you can see Emily over there is, um,
dealing with some customer tickets,
>> which is possible.
>> But then
>> and then there's other guys overseas as
well. So, 24-hour support
>> around the clock.
>> Yeah, correct. So, Bulgaria,
Philippines. This is our product team.
>> So, people here,
>> Gayen,
>> nice to meet you.
>> Hello,
>> D. Nice to meet you. Hello. Hello.
>> Zoe
is here. Uh, but yeah, this is like the
the AAP challengers, the core team.
These guys are working every day, 100%
of the time. A cap challenges living and
breathing.
>> Everything challenge wise. Yeah,
>> everything challenge wise. All the new
product ideas, all the execution, making
sure the dashboards are getting updated,
working new ideas for new products. We
got our partners team here with partners
as well around what partners need from
the challenges. Yeah. Just like
constantly working on the product.
>> Very cool.
>> So, very cool.
>> That's where I sit over there.
>> Partners team. Hello.
>> Hi.
>> Yeah. So they're out there talking to
people bring them in. Also responding to
people like we got a lot of people
inbound
>> inbound requests. People want to join
us. So these guys are
>> communication
>> closers, closers, setters, closes.
>> Setters and closes. That's it. Let me
introduce you to our risk team.
>> Okay.
>> Very important part of our business.
>> Mhm.
>> Uh Jack, Alex.
>> Nice. What happened to your hand, man?
>> Uh heard of playing sport.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Being silly. Little scar.
>> Little scar. Okay. Okay. That's nice. So
you guys you guys are the risk team.
>> Risk team. So risk team, they're not all
here. So we got like risk and options
here, but we've also got a team
offshore.
>> Okay.
>> As well. So they work all closely
together, but they're largely using all
of our like all of our systems, all
automated systems to track trades real
time.
>> Mhm.
>> And then basically making sure that
people are following the rules.
>> Mhm.
>> My payout gets denied. Is this guy's
fault?
>> Yeah. Yeah. He blame [laughter] me.
>> Yeah. So someone doesn't get paid,
you're responsible.
>> Exactly.
>> All right. So you guys don't get paid.
>> Don't mess with Don't mess with
[laughter]
>> Go look for him. Don't mess with this
guy.
He's a big guy.
>> Yeah. I don't know. He broke his hand. I
don't want to know how his the other
guy. [laughter]
>> Okay, cool.
>> Exactly.
>> So, making sure traders aren't breaking
rules and doing everything correctly in
order for them to get a pay.
>> Exactly. Keeping it fair and equitable
for all our traders and making sure
everyone's got the same rules and
conditions applying to them. And yeah,
>> this is my favorite room.
>> Oh, this is my favorite room in the
office. It's got a comfy couch.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Right. Beautiful views.
>> Yeah. This is crazy. You guys literally
have the entire view. We got to like
that be the best view in the best view
in the city.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah.
>> So, uh, everyone's welcome. Everyone's
welcome here.
>> Yeah. I did not expect you guys to have
this many people.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And that's the thing. It's like people
don't realize until they come here.
>> Yeah. Of course. [music]
>> Like the size of this business and like
the the strength and stability
>> of this business. And I think seeing is
believing, right?
>> For sure.
>> So,
>> even for me, I I thought it was AI until
I got here.
>> These people are real. And it's not just
the people here. Like we've got these
other offices as well. So it's a it's a
global team. So
>> and everybody here is W2 full-time 9 to5
or what what's the schedule?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> But they only work during the day or is
there like a team that comes at night as
well?
>> No. No. It's just the day. So people
leave here um probably by about 6:30 the
office is empty.
>> But then our Bulgaria team is online
from about like 5 4 or 5:00 our time and
they work through to midnight. and also
London, UK, Cyprus. So, we got basically
24 hours a day. We got people like
mainly doing customer support ops, make
sure everything's working,
>> right? And and risk.
>> So, when these guys go home, the other
teams turn on
>> 100%. 100%. Yeah. And then the teams are
always talking to each other as well.
>> Very cool.
>> Never never the finished product, right?
Yeah.
>> So, we're always trying to get better.
>> But, um
>> yeah, it's pretty cool. Pretty cool.
>> Yeah. I mean, you have 20 minutes to sit
down.
>> People want to know some questions.
soon. Let's do it.
>> You have like a Can we use one of the 25
board meetings for me?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Let's do it. Let's do it.
>> All right. So, first of all, thank you
very much for having us out here. But
>> absolute pleasure.
>> I am responsible for asking questions.
These are the hard questions.
>> All right. I'm ready. I'm ready.
>> We're basically interrogating you.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. So, we're going to Don't Don't
mind these questions.
>> Okay. So first question is what type of
regulations do you guys have and how
does this benefit the trader in [music]
any way like what do these regulations
do?
>> Perfect. So what these regulations mean
AAB is globally regulated and it's a
globally trusted brand. AAP's globally
regulated by ASICH in Australia, FCA in
the UK and SCIC [music] in the EU. We're
we're governed by those rules. Our
traders get the benefit of that trust
and the credibility that brings. So
basically you guys have to report to
these regulators like once a month for
>> everything that we do as a business is
governed by the rules of those
regulators.
>> Okay. [music]
>> So
>> so if you guys do something unethical or
something wrong, the regulators come
after you guys for whatever reason.
>> Yeah.
>> Correct. Everything's got to be kosher.
>> All right. Next [music] question. Is AAP
Challenges really the only prop firm
that has Trading View as a trading
option?
>> Yeah, we are super excited about Trading
View. Um, and we've just we've [music]
just integrated Trading View with Adap.
We're the only CFD prop firm that offers
Trading View as a direct integration,
which means you come to checkout, you
want to use Trading View, all you do,
you just select Trading View and you
directly integrate it with your through
the AAP tile on Trading View and away
you go.
>> Also, you don't have to go through
MetaTrader, Trade Locker, none of that.
>> No, just direct on Trading View using
the AAP tile. We're directly integrated
and there's nothing else you need to do.
>> Pretty cool.
>> The only prop firm CFD that has that.
Perfect.
>> All right. This next question is very
common nowadays in the industry. I was
not familiar with this, but there's
something called hidden rules.
How many hidden rules do you have? And
what are your exact rules as to why
somebody wouldn't get a payout?
>> Sure. Hidden rules.
>> Yeah.
>> We don't have hidden rules,
>> right?
>> No.
>> I mean, we have rules. Yeah,
>> we have rules, don't get me wrong, but
they're not hidden. I want people to
know what they're actually buying. All
our rules could actually fit on one
page.
>> Can we see Can we Can we see that?
>> Let's print it out.
>> Okay. Um, but it's very simple. Like our
rules are on our website and our FAQs.
Our chatbot has the rules. Like we have
a rules and conditions document which
has like everything. But it's ultimately
is very simple.
>> There you go.
>> Awesome. Thank you. This is literally
this is our rules on a page,
>> right? If if a trader looks at this and
and follows this, they're going to get
paid.
>> Okay. Can I see these rules?
>> So this is every single rule that you
guys have.
>> Yeah. Summarized version, but yeah.
Okay. Profit distribution. No single
trading day profit can exceed 30% or 35%
[music]
of the total reduced profit. Why?
>> Profit distribution basically just means
you can't fluke. You can't just luck
your way into one big trading [music]
day. We actually want to test and prove
that traders are skillful.
>> So this is basically to avoid people
that come in
>> one lucky trade,
>> make a big profit and then that's it.
>> But they haven't actually proven any
skill.
>> Okay, fair enough.
>> Minimum trading days pretty standard.
>> Yeah. payouts. So up to 90% profit share
profit cap 5% on one phase, 10% on two
phase. What is this [music] profit cap?
>> It's consistent with the same principles
around building consistency, discipline,
maintaining your risk profile. This rule
eliminates [music] the incentive for
people to go and do like massive
gambling trades. So, so
>> question right if if I go and I [music]
take a 2% risk on a trade
>> and I catch a 1 to4 risk-to-reward
>> that's essentially going to be past that
[music] 5% on the one stage that means I
would fail I'd be breaching a rule
essentially
>> you wouldn't fail you'll just be
basically we we'd cap the amount that
you can make on a day
>> right
>> but there's nothing to stop you get your
5%
>> okay
>> and then you get your account reset and
then you go again
>> okay
>> right so once you pass Yeah.
>> And you get your payout,
>> your account gets reset and you you're
free to trade again. We want you to go
again.
>> I can make more than 5%.
>> But if I were to make more than that, I
don't get paid more. I don't
>> Correct. Correct.
>> You get Correct.
>> So, so then I just get reset back to the
starting balance.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, that's it.
>> Okay. So, my account doesn't get
>> breached. I just start back
>> stop.
And that's to enforce consistency
>> and to build discipline,
>> risk, manage risk, manage good behavior.
>> Fair enough.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, news trading, I could assume
basically it's because you I want to
avoid people just punting basically.
>> Correct. Very.
>> Yeah. Pretty standard. 10 minutes.
>> Okay. So, you have here permitted
strategies, scalping, swing trading,
EAS, weekend trading. So, yeah,
>> everything outside of this is not
allowed.
>> Correct.
>> Wait, so you guys allow HFT?
>> We allow HFT. We allow EAS. We allow
scalping. We allow swing trading
>> and day trading
>> and weekend trading. You trade over the
weekend.
>> So then these are your restricted
trading strategies.
>> So you don't have
>> money grid trading copy trading is a no
no.
>> Mhm.
>> Account management. You can't give I
can't give my account to you and say
Alex, can you manage my account?
>> Okay. But let's say if I have a 100k
account and a 50k account, I can't copy
trade. Or can I just ask you
>> copy trade yourself?
>> Right. You can copy trade your own your
own account as much as you want. Go go
go for your life. You can't be trading
for somebody else. Right. So, we can't
have you impersonating other people.
>> Is that it?
>> That's it.
>> That's it. There's nothing else. So, if
they break any of these rules, they will
have to start again.
>> Correct. Or they'll have their account
breached, right? They'll either be reset
back to the beginning. So, some of these
are a soft breach, some of them are hard
breach. Soft breach basically means you
don't lose your account, but your
account will get reset back to the
beginning and you'll get a warning. So
essentially it's like a yellow card and
then a hard bridge like a red card your
account you lose your account it's a
it's a no for people who really want to
get into the detail we have actually
have a document that like a like a legal
document that has everything written out
so people are welcome to read that we
want people to read the rules take the
time to read the rules right familiarize
yourself and then trade
>> so outside of this there's no hidden
rules
>> nothing sneaky
>> nothing sneaky [music]
>> so if everybody follows these rules you
essentially guarantee they're going to
get a payout
>> if people pass the challenges
legitimately and they haven't broken
[music] the rules, we want to pay them
out. That's the whole point.
>> So, as long as they don't break these
rules, it's a guaranteed payout,
>> right?
>> I mean,
>> yeah,
>> it's not it's very simple in my opinion.
Okay, cool.
>> Next question. This is the question that
everybody wants to know and the main
reason why I came here. When traders
pass their funded account and they are
funded, are these traders actually being
backed with real funds or are they not?
Are you paying people out out of the
signup money or is there real backing
behind these traders?
>> The traders who are operating in in the
payout stage are 100% operating in live
market conditions. But are we are we
backing their trades one for one, right,
in real time? No. But what we are doing,
we've got thousands of traders in the
live conditions and [music] we're
aggregating that data. We're looking at
data from a risk point of view. We got a
risk team that I introduced you to
before and they are hedging that based
on based on the data that's happening,
based on the trades that are happening.
They're hedging that data in real time
and [music] developing a quantum
strategy around that that we're actually
making profit on that from a aggregate
point of view.
>> Okay. So, for example, let's say I just
got funded on a two-step challenge. I
have 50K funded account. I put 10 lots
on gold, right? Like I click buy on
gold, whatever. Is that trade being
backed exactly as I just placed it on
that account?
>> No, it's not. But we have thousands of
traders as I said in aggregate making
those trades.
>> Okay.
>> Right. So, we can use that data to
actually assess what's happening at an
aggregate scale and supply strategies to
to make money from that.
>> Okay. So, so you don't make money
exactly off of each trader, but it's the
accumulation of all these traders that
lead you
>> to be able to make your own decisions as
to Okay. Correct. So you're not directly
making money from your from your trade,
but indirectly we are.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> So yeah. So you still technically need
those traders to take trades for the
business to function and for you guys to
have an edge basically.
>> 100% because we're using that we're
using the data that we're getting from
the thousands of traders that are that
are that are operating to inform our
risk management.
>> Okay.
>> So I mean yeah like that that does make
sense. Like you aren't making profit.
For example, let's say someone makes on
a 50k account they make 10% they make
5,000 bucks. Let's say they want to
withdraw 50% of that. Those 2500 bucks
weren't made exactly from their specific
account, right? Like so those 2500 bucks
that you're going to pay them out
doesn't come from their funded account.
It comes from the bigger strategy out of
all these traders. Is that what it is?
So my next question is running the
business model like this. Why won't this
business fail or what are the odds of
this business failing of running the
business model like this?
>> We're a business. I mean every business
has the risk of failing right but you've
seen you've you've walked around our
business you've seen the real people the
end to end of everything that we're
doing from risk operations marketing
product tech safet um security legal
compliance all those teams are real
they're here in the flesh but that
doesn't guarantee anything right we
still have to operate with with rigorous
processes follow the law apply good
business sense and if we fail it means
that our T1 banking partners our global
T1 independent auditors have missed
something. Our insurance, all of those
reputable global players, right, that
are working with us, our counterparties
have also missed something. So, we have
all the protections in place that anyone
could reasonably expect. And I challenge
any other prop firm in this space to ask
anyone else whether they have the same
infrastructure that we have. But
ultimately, we still need to run a
profitable business where we manage our
costs responsibly and we make sure that
we're at the end of the day making
profit for our shareholders. But we're
trying to be responsible corporate
citizens and put a great product out
there that people want to buy. There
would have to be something that goes
wrong.
>> Yeah.
>> For us to fail, right?
>> Five different regulators have to miss
something. Correct.
>> At the same time,
>> correct? You know, we've got the
regulation in place. We've got the funds
segregated with JP Morgan Chase. We have
all the reasonable steps to give this
thing the best possible chance.
>> It's fair enough for me. You know, I
don't I'm I'm trying to be the haters
right now. [laughter] I'm trying to be
the haters in the comments.
>> At the end of the day, it comes back to
delivery. saying what you're going to do
and doing what you said you were going
to do and being boring in some ways.
Like I want to be boring. I want people
I want people to know what they're going
to get. No surprises, transparency
and trust what they're going to get,
right? Cuz ultimately it's about trust.
It's about repeatability. It's about
deliverability. It's about knowing what
you're going to get and just doing that
over and over again. But that's how good
business is run. Doing the basics well.
That's what we want to do.
>> So the odds of the business failing or
someone not getting a payout, very low
>> basically. I mean there's always going
to be people that don't get a payout,
right? But again, if you come back to
the rules, they've done something. They
either haven't read the rules, they
don't know the rules, or they haven't or
they've broken the rules. So, yeah, we
have a risk team that's in place to to
keep those people out because the rules
are there for a reason, but if you
follow the rules, you'll get paid. Next
question. Why do you guys charge money
for a challenge? If you make profits
from the strategy of the traders, what's
the point of charging people for a
challenge in the first place?
>> Sure. I mean, you've seen our business,
right? You've seen we got real people
here actually managing managing the
business. People cost money. The trades
are in real life conditions, right? So
that costs money. We got trading
platforms. We got bridge fees, got
operational costs. You know, we're
running a endto-end business. All of
those costs help us with essentially
covering the cost of running the
business and allow us to do what we do,
right? Which is basically bringing the
opportunity to people to trade our
simulator trading product across the
best platforms in the world. We got MT5,
got MT4, Trading View, and Trade Locker.
If you're in a country though where
where we allow traders, we're basically
giving you a premium experience to buy a
challenge that you know is going to be
backed by air cap.
>> So technically you don't use sign up
money to pay the traders out, right?
>> Yeah. So we use the signup money to
cover the cost of running the business
which is all the cost that I mentioned
before
>> which is our overheads, trading
platforms, everything like that to bring
the product to the customer.
>> Guys, I'm asking every single possible
question. Next question. So I have a
couple like flash bang out questions. Do
you guys have trading draw down?
>> Trailing? No. I hate trailing draw down.
I think it's deceptive and I and I
really don't like it. It's not good for
traders and so we don't use it.
>> Okay.
>> Why don't you guys have instant payouts?
>> Instant payouts. Again, I think I
mentioned earlier we have a risk team.
The risk team has a job and part of
their job is to actually check payouts
and make sure people haven't broken
rules. We need to allow 24 hours for our
risk team to do their job.
>> Make sure that everything
>> basically make sure traders are
following the rules. With instant
payouts, we can't do that. So I see that
you guys have some custom feature coming
called the revive feature, right? So I
know you guys were talking to me about
earlier. What is this revive feature and
what is it? What does it do?
>> Sure. Bridget, you want to talk about
revive?
>> Sure.
>> So now we're offering insurance that
allow clients to just try a reset when
they are on the phase one or phase two
during one phase and two phase
challenges. Revive is going to be for
funded accounts payout stage. So clients
are going to be able to reset their
accounts when they are on the live
stage. So that is going to give them
another opportunity to actually be close
to get a payout.
>> So if their account is in draw down on
the funded stage, they can revive it or
if they fail, they can pay to revive it.
>> No, they need to get the revive before
they fail.
>> M
>> so when you go at the checkout, you're
going to get this add-on.
>> So that's how you're going to get this
feature. You go to the payout stage and
you can use it if you fail.
>> So let's say that your account went to
draw down. You're lost, but you have the
revive. So, you're going to be able to
actually continue on your payout stage.
So, you don't need to get a new
challenge.
>> So, you could only get the revive before
you start the challenge essentially
>> at this point. Yes. But we have a
surprise that is it's going to come up
soon.
>> All right. That's pretty [__] cool in
my opinion. [laughter]
Next question. What exactly is the day
trader challenge? I know you guys have
like this like hour challenge or
whatever. It's pretty cool. I don't know
what it consists of. Talk to me about
it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, we had people who wanted a
quick challenge, right? They want to do
a challenge on the way home on their
commute on the way home from work or at
the gym and and it suits the way they
trade, right? Same day challenge. So, we
created this challenge. It's the only
challenge like this in the market. It's
fully customizable. You can start as low
as $5. You can choose you can choose
your conditions and that's it, right? 1
hour, 2 hour, 4 hour, 8 hour, and fully
customizable challenge. Away you go.
Finish in one day, get paid the next
day. That's it.
>> Is it these same exact rules or does it
have its own unique rules?
>> It's not the same rules. There's two
rules. Basically, the first rule is
there's a time limit on it. So, if you
take a 1-hour challenge, the challenge
starts and it ends in an hour, right?
So, if you hit your profit target within
an hour, you win. If not, you don't you
don't you don't win the challenge. The
only rule I want to highlight to you is
what we call the profit allocation rule.
Basically means that you can't make all
of your profit on one single asset,
right? So, you have to trade at least
two different asset types and at least
three instruments. You can't win all
your money on gold, for example, right?
You have to trade gold and forex for
example.
>> So I would have to trade currencies and
then
>> and commodities
>> and commodities.
>> Yeah. Or currencies and crypto.
>> That makes it a little bit harder,
>> but it's still a fun challenge, right?
And you can still do it in in your, you
know, in your afternoon, right? You can
take multiple challenge in the same day,
and if you pass, you get paid the next
day. 100% profit split.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, not bad.
>> I mean, yeah, it's a it's a little I
mean, it's a challenge. It's meant to be
challenging, right? So, it's not the
easiest.
>> But if I can tell you you can 10x your
money, right, in 1 hour, that shouldn't
be easy
>> for sure,
>> right? Equally, if you have the
opportunity to 2x your money in 1 hour
or even in 8 hours, you know, that
should be easier than making 10x your
money. But again, it's doable. And we
have traders currently who are doing
great, who love this challenge.
>> Do you have any questions, Sarah? I
don't know. I I ran out of questions. I
don't have any more questions. Like, I
have all I got have other basic
questions, but I feel like you answered
the hard nitty-gritty questions. Yeah.
You're welcome to ask more questions and
we can just do more stuff if you want or
I don't know.
>> All right, bro. What a long day. I think
it was great. Look, it's it's night
time. We've been here like
>> Yeah, we did a lot of talking and a lot
of interrogation. Yeah, honestly when
the cameras turned off is like where
they really showed us a lot of the
backend stuff because they don't want to
put on video stuff behind the business.
I wouldn't want to do it either. So very
cool to see the way the infrastructure
is in the back end,
>> but we at least know it's a real place
now.
>> Yeah, it's definitely real. And like how
how they manage a team of 100 people,
which is honestly insane. Um just
everything in general. they actually
have an advantage that they are here
technically in the future because they
get to work around the clock almost like
in advance. Like for example, let's say
right now for them it's Friday, but it's
still Thursday in the States. So they
can work on something while everybody's
sleeping in the States and when they
wake up it's already done. Very cool. So
yeah, had a great time. Now we're going
to head back home and get some rest
because I'm fried.
>> Yeah, I'm fried. [music] Yeah, I'm
fried. Yeah, I'm fried. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm f
>> Wait, are you the really rich guy?
>> Oh my god.
>> Really rich guy.
>> What? With the smash spaghetti?
>> Yeah.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> Matt Armstrong's fixing spaghetti.
>> Yeah.
>> Let's go.
>> What are you guys doing? You riding?
>> Yeah, just riding around.
>> You know how to wheelie or no?
>> Oh, yeah. I can.
>> You can?
>> Yeah. Okay. Let me see.
Oh.
>> Oh, your turn.
>> Oh, you're that guy in the group.
>> Okay. Okay. Oh. Oh,
>> yeah. That was good. That was [laughter]
>> I'm sorry.
>> Good. Good meeting you guys.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah. Say y'all.
>> Are you that really rich guy? I've never
heard that one.
>> Yeah. He's not lying. I mean, yeah, he's
not, but there's a lot more to me than
just a meeting. Whatever. Point is,
we're trying to right now find the spot
for the meet and greet that we're going
to be doing tomorrow. So, I did not
expect to do a meet and greet here at
all, but I think I've received over
3,000 DMs. But the reason why I want to
do the meet and greet, not only is it to
meet all the Aussies, but I want to ask
the traders in person, like look, this
is what I found out yesterday. What else
do you want to know or come to the
conclusion before I sign this deal with
this prop firm? Maybe they have other
questions that I haven't thought of for
whatever reason and they helped me get
to the bottom of it. So yeah, we're
looking for the spot right now where we
can meet the Aussies mate here in
Australia.
>> You know, we can't leave Australia until
we see a kangaroo.
>> Oh, I mean are the kangaroos just like
anywhere? Are they
>> Yeah, they're like they're like roosters
in Helia.
>> Ooh. Hey mate, where where can I find
kangaroos?
>> Yeah, kangaroos like they're not close
to here.
>> No, we need to go into the bush.
>> How far is that?
>> Plenty road. Plenty. Uh George, we found
a lot.
>> How far is that?
>> How far? Oh, we need to catch a train. A
train?
>> Yes.
>> How far is that?
>> Uh about 1 hour.
>> 1 hour. Okay, that's not bad.
>> 1 1 hour. 1 hour and a half. We're going
to we're going to we're chefs, so we
want to cook a kangaroo. Will we catch
him or no?
>> Try.
>> Good luck.
>> Okay. Any advice?
>> Uh I never did, so I don't know.
>> I can't recommend. Okay.
>> This guy's like, "What the fuck?"
[laughter]
>> They eat them. What? Catch him. Eat
them. What the [__]
>> We find ourselves at a park.
Seas thinks that he is stronger than I
am. Has a stronger grip.
We're going to put that to the test
right now. So, we're going to do a
hanging competition. Whoever can hang
the longest without falling wins. 100
bucks competition.
>> You lost 100 bucks, buddy.
>> I'll see you in an economy.
>> You're so cooked.
>> I'm ready whenever you are.
>> You ready? All right.
Is it
[laughter]
[music]
Oh, this showing, bro. Like, it's pretty
It's pretty bad, brother.
Yeah, my hands going to get really bad.
See that?
I I genuinely enjoy that, though. I was
having a great time. Yeah, that was
actually I wouldn't say fun, but
>> more enjoyable, but
>> I don't like working out with weights,
bro. Well, you know this. By the way, I
go to the gym and I do 15 minutes worth
of workout. All I like doing is just
pull-ups, dips, and push-ups. That's it.
All right. So, this is the spot right
here. So, we had the bright idea that
I'm going to bring my laptop. I'm going
to be right here.
>> I did not expect that.
>> Yeah, you shouldn't slam your laptop on
there.
>> Yeah. that that won't be a good idea.
Well, the point is we're going to have
another trader right here asking them
what questions do they have about
trading and what other insights do they
want about the prop firm? Like what
other doubts, what other concerns, what
other things do they want to see? And I
can be their voice and go speak to Adam
tomorrow and get more of these questions
answered. So, I think this is this Bro,
I'm just cold, dude. We got to come with
a jacket tomorrow. But imagine we come
here tomorrow and there's like two
Aussies. Oh, man. That'd be depressing.
At least we know two Aussies
>> and At least you know what? We'll take
those two Aussies out to a good time.
>> What if it's like a thousand Aussies?
>> Then that's an issue.
>> Then that then we just leave.
>> This is a good spot, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Am I overthinking it? Like it's pretty
cinematic, right? You got the little
bench.
>> It's like a bench for like only two
people.
>> Okay. That's all I need. All I need is
one person and then people could be
around ask you know supervising. All
right. So tomorrow 2 p.m. We're going to
be right back here answering any
questions from the locals. See you boys
tomorrow.
>> You look like a mermaid.
>> Very majestic on your part.
>> You know I used to swim back in high
school.
>> I had to make my Cuban as an ancestors.
This is how you know it's way too early.
My Cuban ancestors happy. We are
extremely jetlagged. It is currently
4:00 in the morning, bro. We We've only
been here for 3 days and we've done the
same thing every day. The Ritz where we
are here to the office and back. That's
it. Pretty excited for the meet and
greet later today. Hopefully, I don't
fall asleep in the middle of the day
like I've been doing every day. So, yep.
Pretty much this is going to be
essentially like our last day here
because we leave on Sunday night, Monday
morning back to Miami. 26-hour journey
back. And it's very important that I get
to ask people the question, what else do
you guys want to know? And what else do
you guys want to see from AAP side, the
platform side? What guys do you what do
you want to see from the trading floor?
Because in the trading floor, ladies and
gentlemen, I'm not going to lie, I got a
lot of more ideas from what I just saw
at the office. Very inspiring to me. I'm
very glad that I did that. Changed my
vision entirely. And I want to show you
guys some updates of how swing trading
lab trading floor is looking like. All
right. So, we've been getting some video
updates right here of just do this
of how this is essentially like the
parking lot in front of the warehouse.
How that's looking. That was 50,000.
How the basketball court is getting
painted. That was 25,000. This is
actually 40,000 and 40,000 each one.
These are all just like video updates
how that's looking. These are the in
front of the warehouse.
Let me find pictures of inside the
trading floor, which is what matters,
right? Oh, the other warehouse is
getting insulation done so it doesn't
get hot. All right. So, this is the gym.
You see this is the gym. Putting
insulation on all the walls inside of
the trading floor. The guys are watching
the World Cup.
>> That's the guy building our house.
>> That's the guy building the house, bro.
>> We're working on it. It's getting done.
Shit's getting done. And the main reason
why we're rushing things is because July
25th, I'm hosting an events there for
just my students. So, we have a hundred
students that have already confirmed
showing up to this event where it's
basically going to be a whole day thing.
It's only for my community because I
want to be able to have a one-on-one
experience for everybody that comes. And
this is not really a commercialized
property. It's not open to the public.
This is private. And I want to be able
to dedicate to people that actually care
to learn and want to really give this
100% of their efforts. I want to give
those people the time of day and
actually help them throughout the
journey. So, if this were to be
commercialized and available to
everybody, it takes away that value
aspect of it. So, this is only private
and exclusive to just my students. And I
do two events a year with my students in
person. And instead of going to go rent
somewhere, try to do it right there. We
could definitely accommodate 100
students. I wanted to do 200, but my
team told me, "No, only do 100." Just
the first one. We don't know if the
Starlink Wi-Fi is going to break and
nobody's going to have service. So, just
the first one to test.
>> And I know this sounds like a very cool
and powerful idea. This took me a lot of
time to really put together and I think
there's a reason why nobody's ever done
it because it's a very powerful idea
that gets executed correctly. If there's
someone that's going to execute it
correctly, it's going to be me. Like I
am very persistent. I take big risk.
I've been in jail two times for the
brand, you know, streaking the Super
Bowl and doing other crazy stuff. Like I
put my life at risk for the brand
multiple times and I don't have to like
I'm respectfully like the kid said that
rich guy you [laughter] know like I'm
good but I love the drive. I love
working towards something. So if at any
point the trading floor closes for
unexpected reasons it is not because I
did it. We got attacked by the matrix.
Just know that if I put together too
many successful people and uh we start
doing too many big things we might make
some people upset. But that's a lot of
information for this very moment. I'm
going to have a swim and uh go hit the
sauna or something cuz it's 4:30 in the
morning.
>> Are Australians usually on time to
things or are they typically late?
>> Yeah,
>> most of them they're okay.
>> most of them. But a lot of them can be
late as well.
>> Yeah.
>> Feel like it's a culture everywhere,
right? To be late to things.
>> It just depends how late.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow. There's a lot more I thought.
>> [laughter]
>> Nobody bought a kangaroo.
>> How you doing?
>> How's it going?
>> Oh, what's the honest?
>> I don't know if you had this many.
>> What up, boys? Good.
>> All right. Good to see you. What's going
on, guys?
>> You guys know each other or is the first
time you guys all meet?
>> It's kind of cool. You guys get to meet
other traders here.
>> Pretty cool. Pretty cool.
>> Well, Welcome. [laughter]
>> Got your little gift.
>> Oh, wow. Thank you.
>> Welcome to Australia.
>> Thank you very much. What is this
exactly?
>> Oh, these are like probably the famous
biscuits from Australia. Every American
generally likes them. So,
>> it's like a like a chocolate from here.
Like a local chocolate.
>> Yeah, I don't eat them. I'm too fat.
But, uh,
>> you sure you don't eat them? [laughter]
>> But enjoy them.
>> Thank you very much, brother. I
appreciate it. If
>> no one takes it, we're going to stash it
in here.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Now, would you ever do a 100 to a
million challenge again? [laughter]
>> I don't know, man. I don't know. I don't
know.
>> What broker do you use that allows you
to do big lot size like that?
>> Is that LK?
>> I use LQH1X. I use IC and OA. So, I use
like four different brokers.
>> But would I do another one again? Maybe.
I don't know.
>> That's right. That was crazy. I followed
you through that because one of your
students as well
>> and I literally just flipped an account
like I was seeing these numbers.
Couldn't even believe my eyes.
>> So you saw the whole journey of that?
>> Yeah, the whole journey and Alex take so
many so many
>> like balls of steel to put like
literally like 500k literally like
trying to double it.
>> I mean it was like a year and a half but
it it went down.
>> Insane. Insane.
>> How do you get rid of that fear of
thinking you're not going to make it or
not requesting a payout? How do you get
past that barrier? It's actually a lot
harder for me than it is for you guys.
Like when I got started trading, nobody
did this like at all. I did not meet a
group of traders. It was just me by
myself. So I pretty much have to believe
in myself. Like you have other people
around you. Like who here has made
profits from the markets like raise your
hand. So that should take away your fear
if somebody next to you has made some
type of profits. You know, I never had
that when I started in my journey. I was
just by myself.
>> Thank you very much.
>> I lost money. We lost money. [laughter]
Everybody's lost money.
>> Alex, um, if you would start again with
having that knowledge that you've got
right now and you would start from
ground zero, like probably most of us
from here, it takes money to make money.
>> How would you start from ground zero
building up that capital to then
possibly trading your life?
>> Yeah, definitely prop firms. No, I mean,
for me, I was two years unsuccessful
with personal accounts. I was just
constantly trying to chase that big
account flip in order for me to deem
myself profitable. And I was a
successful trader at that point and that
never worked. Came across platforms,
failed probably for six months. Then I
learned how to manage risk. I learned
how to follow rules when nobody was
looking. And then I figured out, okay, I
need to follow these rules, manage
larger amounts of capital. And then I
built my personal account. So I've been
in my personal account probably for like
four or five years now. I haven't traded
prop firms. I haven't had the need to.
But if I were have to start from zero,
build capital. Prop firms is definitely
the easiest way. sucks because you have
some rules, you know, that they are
meant to challenge you on purpose, but
that would be the best way possible for
sure.
>> Any prop friend that you can suggest us?
>> I mean, that's what I came here for.
[laughter]
>> Holy [__] WHAT UP? WHAT UP? WHAT UP,
>> DUDE? Nobody brought a kangaroo, bro.
It's kind of disappointing. I'm not
going to lie. [music]
>> What you're doing with Bugatti is
actually mad, man. You know, you're
doing a big movement like
>> Yeah.
>> I know it's not trading, but I've been
working on Lambos, Ferraris for all my
life.
>> Okay.
>> And what they ask you to pay for like
>> No. Yeah.
>> You know, I the Bugatti should be done
next month, hopefully.
>> No, I'm going to show you guys how it's
going to look.
>> You got a picture?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'll show you guys. I'll
show you.
>> Sick.
>> All right. So, this is what it's going
to look like.
>> All right. Well, we can't wait.
>> No. No pictures. Yeah. No. Matt would
get so mad if I [laughter]
No pictures. All right. No, no. I see
your phone, bro.
>> All right, let me see your hands.
Everybody show me your [__] hands.
[laughter]
>> That's [__]
>> That look like
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's It's going to be way
better than before.
>> I'm one of your students that said I
forget.
>> Oh, thank you, brother.
>> I'm actually about to post you on there.
I'll be like, I have to see with Alex.
[laughter]
>> Thank you, brother. Thank you for
coming, bro. I actually got both of your
programs, set and forget and uh you know
no BS.
>> Fire. I haven't seen you in the no BS
yet.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm in there
because cuz I work full-time as well,
you know, trying to juggle between the
two. So I study at night time.
>> You've been on the calls with Maicio and
Sebastian or
>> Yeah. Yeah. Mauricio. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So, you know, uh Yeah, man. Loving it,
you know.
>> Brother, thank you very much.
>> Can't wait. I'm you know, trying to get
trying to get down to your, you know,
your new studios
>> for the trading floor. Yeah. We're going
to you're going to go
>> I want to come, man. Yeah, I think you
should come. You know, the 25th.
>> Every all the students are invited.
You're welcome to come.
>> Yeah. Looking forward to
>> the tickets are inside of the community.
>> I I came here to say thank you for your
inspiration. I'm one of your student. I
move from New Zealand to here just
because of the trading. I left my
everything business house and everything
>> and I was following your 100 mill as
well.
>> Thank you very much. and your course I
received from for my one of the birthday
gift from my wife in my 40.
>> Okay, cool. She's a keeper.
>> I don't necessarily trade like your
style. [laughter]
>> I'm a crazy voice, bro.
>> I don't necessarily trade your style,
but set and forget has really helped my
psychology and just letting [__] run and
like letting [__] play out.
>> So, appreciate you, my man.
>> Thank you very much.
>> Traders, but you reckon I could get a
flip?
>> Sure. Your voice should be like on a
documentary or something, bro. People
were saying like podcast.
>> He should be at He should do your
documentary.
>> Yeah. Like a podcast or something.
>> Let me know. Let me know. [__]
>> I was in a rush.
>> It's a crazy voice.
>> We look good.
>> Yeah, we look good.
>> Do we sound good,
>> boys? I wish I had more time. Thank you
guys very much for coming out. All the
support. Love every single one of you
guys. And I will see you guys soon. I'll
be back in Melbourne soon, boys.
>> See you, boys.
>> Have a good one.
>> I'll see you in Miami.
>> See you boys.
next time.
>> What do you think of ICT?
>> [__] him. [laughter]
>> [__] him.
[music]
[laughter]
What the hell?
Yo, [laughter] this guy is
>> Dude, you almost hit your car, bro.
>> Almost. [laughter]
>> Almost.
>> This limo is sick. You know, we um
What's your name, sir?
>> Gary.
>> Gary, you know, we just blew one up.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah. I bought one and I blew it up.
>> Oh my god.
>> This This was gangster.
>> This one's gi six wheel
>> chopping [laughter] up, bro. Why is that
back tire like that?
>> Ladies and gentlemen, finally back home
after a 26-hour journey, [laughter]
dude. We could have just signed
something through Docu Sign and like
that's really it, bro. Like, we didn't
have to go all the way over there. We
know we're not those guys. We're not
those guys. We do things differently
here at Swing Trading Lab. Clearly, like
take longer than we should to have the
trading floor open, ladies and
gentlemen. Now, I want to obviously give
you by the time you guys are watching
this video, I'm sure you already know,
but we have officially partnered up with
ACAP funding to bring challenges to
everybody that comes to the trading
floor. So, they're managing personal
capital. So, they're managing prop
capital and what we are scaling with our
own capital here at Swing Trading Lab.
So, so you want to get your AAP
challenges discount code down below. You
guys already know I went the extra mile
to make sure that they are regulated,
that there is people there in person,
that they're running a legitimate
business model. I asked all the hard
questions. I even did the meet and
greet, asked the people in the meet and
greet to give me more hard questions to
go back and speak to them. And uh I
mean, for me, I'm very happy. If you
guys have any other questions you would
like to ask them, feel free to reach out
to the support. but love the fact that
they're the only prop firm that opened
the doors to me and allowed me to go and
ask these tough questions and be able to
be as transparent as they were. So,
little update on trading floor.
Currently on the final stages, just
furniture is really what's missing. This
is the hangout area. That's the
educational side over here. Let me show
you guys. By the way, that wall right
there is actually going to be purely for
payout certificates. So, everybody that
gets a payout from AAP Challenges will
go on that wall right there. So, they're
going to get their own certificate that
goes on that wall. They're going to be
sending us a logo. The brokers that I
trade with are going to be on this wall.
So, anybody that has a successful
account flip is going to go on this wall
with their flipping certificate. And
then over here are the actual traders.
In my opinion, I think this is much
cooler, much cleaner, and I just think
it's better in my opinion. I have one of
these. Obviously, these are massive. I
don't think people like screens this
big, but I'm going to be providing this
for all the traders that come here,
desk, laptop, keyboard, and everything.
And ladies and gentlemen, that's pretty
much what this video consisted of, of
going the extra mile and seeing behind
the scenes of one of the largest prop
firms in the industry. It's a very
sketchy industry lately because a lot of
these prop firms just come up one year,
take everybody's money, and then run
off. And a lot of bad businesses have
been built on the backbone of a good
opportunity for traders. And there's
great businesses that sometimes don't
get all the attention that they should
because of the type of common issues
that the industry has like the ones that
we've already discussed. So yeah, I hope
you guys enjoyed this video. Really did
this one for you guys. This took a lot
of my time. This took This whole trip
was like $60,000 by the way. I know. I
know. You know,
>> I I did not feel that in the seat that I
was sitting on in the
>> Yeah, because we missed a flight, bro.
Cuz you [__] drove slow, bro. From
[__] the R. But, you know, it's okay,
man. It's a It's a team effort. But
aside from that, I had a great time. Got
to meet the guys, other like-minded
people. And I got a lot of cool ideas to
do here for this trading floor. So, if
you guys like this video, hit that like,
comment, and subscribe. And ladies and
gentlemen, trading floor. By the next
time you guys see the next video, we'll
be done. So, hope you guys enjoyed it.
I'll see you guys in the next one.
>> Other than Adam.
>> Oh, dude. That was [__] Matt
Armstrong with his [__] ads, bro.
Dude, [__] this guy. I haven't finished
my Bugatti
and he's charging us ads.